Now let's start combining the strips of our image.
What we want to do, is we want to take one strip and then make some room to put the first strip of the second image, and then take the strip of the first image, put it next to that, and keep alternating as you go along, and it's going to be one long picture with alternating strips from each image.
The important thing over here is just to keep everything in order.
Make sure that you're putting the strips one after the other in the right consecutive order, otherwise it gets a little--the finished product won't work, and it gets a little confusing if you--if you don't take note as you're putting in the images.
One of the signs that you should look for when completing the interchanging of the strips, is that you've started with one image, the first image, and you've actually ended with the last piece being from the second image.
And that's one indication to know that you actually combined the image properly.
Also it's important to maybe when you create the image, images, knowing that you're going to have to interchange them like this, to make them very distinct colors or possibly a different, a different type of shape or image entirely, so that this part of the project doesn't get too confusing.
But we see that we've combined all the images, all the different shapes, and now we're going to put these together.
We're going to carefully flip it over and put tape so that all of these strips stick together, and then it's going to be folded up like an accordion shape, and once it's folded up it will become half its size, and then we'll be able to put it directly on a piece of regular white paper, the same size as the original image.
So that's what we're going to do next.
So, so far in this step I've shown you how to take your images and place them, interchange them, each strip from one image to the next, to make a long mixed image that is going to be folded up.